Fenil Mehta

WEB DEVELOPER (MERN)









https://www.linkedin.com /in/mehtafenil/

+91 7738100952

fenil.code@gmail.com

https://itsfenil.github.io/Portfolio/

Summary

I'm a web developer by day, and a code wizard by night. I've built websites from scratch, designed logos, Painting, and created stunning visuals that would make Picasso jealous. When I'm not busy slaying pixels, you can find me tinkering with MERN and React projects. My skills may be diverse, but my dedication to crafting top-notch digital experiences is unmatched.

Education

2021 - 2024

B.TECH, COMPUTER SCIENCE & ENGINEERING

Parul University

2019 - 2021

DIPLOMA, DIPLOMA IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

Viva College Of Diploma Engineering & Technology (New) Percentage: 87.00%

Expertise's

- UI/UX Intermediate
- Visual Design Intermediate
- Figma Intermediate
- Photoshop Intermediate
- JavaScript Intermediate
- HTML Intermediate
- CSS Intermediate
- React Intermediate
- MERN Intermediate
- Git / GitHub Intermediate
- Bootstrap Intermediate

Soft Skills

Hobbies

- Communication
- Dance
- Teamwork
- Digital Painting
- Time Management
- Coding
- Problem solving
- Exploring new Skills
- Fast Learner
- **Reading Comics**
- Leadership
- Learning

Experiences

Nov 2022 - Jan 2023

WEB DEVELOPMENT AND BRANDING CONSULTANT (FREELANCE) -**AADI SOLUTION WEBSITE AND SOCIAL MEDIA MANAGEMENT**

https://aadisolution.com/

As a freelance web developer and branding consultant, I designed AADI Solution logo and built their company website from scratch using HTML and CSS. Additionally, I created and managed their Instagram and Facebook pages, created Instagram posts and videos, and assisted with Facebook meta business. Completed the project on time and received positive feedback from the client.

April 2023 - Present

WEB DEVELOPMENT AND BRANDING CONSULTANT (FREELANCE) -PHOENIX HOUSE OF PUBLICATION WEBSITE AND BRANDING

https://pheonixhouseofpublication.co.in/

As a freelance web developer and branding consultant, I assisted Phoenix House of Publication in establishing their online presence by designing their logo, renaming the company, and developing their website from scratch. Utilizing HTML, CSS, and other tools, I created a responsive website that reflects the company's values and brand identity.

Sep 2022 - Sep 2023

WEB DEVELOPMENT (COLLABORATION) - NINESHOP JEWELRY WEBSITE **DEVELOPMENT**

Company: Five Online Web Solutions Pvt. Ltd.

Collaborated with Five Online Web Solutions Pvt. Ltd. to develop a new jewelry website for Nineshop using WordPress. Built the website from scratch with e-commerce functionality and a responsive design. Completed the project within the agreed timeline and received positive feedback from the client.

Oct 2022 - Jan 2023

WEB DEVELOPMENT, DIGITAL CONTENT CREATION, AND DIGITAL PAINTING (FREELANCE) - MISSIONJPR NGO

https://missionjpr.org/

Built a website for the NGO MissionJPR using WordPress, including a donation system, blog section, and photo gallery. Provided video and audio editing, digital painting, and designed marketing materials including the logo, videos, and images.

Nov 2022 - Feb 2023

RESPONSIVE TODO LIST (PERSONAL)

MONGODB, EXPRESS JS, REACT JS, NODE JS (MERN)

https://shorturl.at/fsAPX

Aug 2022- Oct 2022

CRYPTO HUNTER (PERSONAL) REACT JS, COINGECKO API

https://crypto-hunter-react.netlify.app/

Real-time cryptocurrency tracker with prices, rankings, market cap, and price history charts in USD and INR. Stay up-to-date with 24-hour, 30-day, 3-month, and 1-year price movements.

Internship

Feb 2023 - April 2023

WEB DEVELOPMENT INTERN AT AADI SOLUTION, FEB 2023

As a web development intern at Aadi Solution, I worked on building and designing websites using HTML and CSS, Js and React.js. Completed various tasks assigned by my supervisors and gained valuable experience in the field of web development.